[Diana] Some days,
my childhood feels so very far away.
And others,
I can almost see it.
The magical land of my youth,
like a beautiful dream of
when the whole world felt like a promise
and the lessons that lay ahead
yet unseen.
Looking back, [chuckles]
I wish I'd listened.
Wish I'd watched more closely
and understood.
But sometimes you can't see
what you're learning
until you come out the other side.
[crowd cheering]
[urges horse] Come on!
- [grunts]
- [crowd cheers]
- [all cheering]
- Come on!
[panting]
[rider Amazon] Come on!
[grunts]
[all cheering]
I'm gonna miss out.
I've seen this contest
humble even the most
seasoned warriors, Diana.
I can do it.
Just do your best.
And remember,
greatness is not what you think.
Pace yourself and watch.
[gong ringing]
[crowd cheering]
[Young Diana grunting]
- [grunts]
- [yelps]
[panting]
[urges horse]
[grunts]
[crowd cheering]
[horse whinnies]
- [groans]
- [horse whinnies]
[panting]
- [riders urging horses]
- [horse whinnies]
[gasps]
[Young Diana grunts]
[crowd cheering]
No!
[both grunt]
[crowd cheering]
[both whooping]
[Young Diana] No!
That's not fair!
No.
No. But...
- You took the short path.
- [Young Diana] But...
- You cheated, Diana.
- No.
But that...
That is the truth.
That is the only truth,
and truth is all there is.
But I would've won, if you didn't...
But you didn't.
You cannot be the winner,
because you are not ready to win,
and there is no shame in that.
[sighs tearfully]
Only in knowing the truth in your heart
and not accepting it.
No true hero is born from lies.
[Young Diana crying]
Your time will come, Diana.
When?
When you're ready.
Look to the Golden Warrior Asteria.
She did not become a legend
out of haste.
She did it through true acts of bravery.
Like patience, diligence,
and the courage to face the truth.
[sighs]
One day, you'll become
all that you dream of and more,
and everything will be different.
This world is not yet ready
for all that you will do.
[Maxwell on TV] Welcome to the future.
Life is good, but it can be better.
And why shouldn't it be?
Everything we've ever dreamed about
- is right at our fingertips.
- [woman chattering]
But are you reaping the rewards?
Do you...
- [both whooping]
- ...have it all?
[passenger] Slow down, dude.
No way.
- [both gasp]
- [brakes screeching]
[tires screeching]
[both screaming]
[panicked chattering]
[both] Dude!
[Maxwell] Welcome to
Black Gold Cooperative.
- Oh, my gosh. Guys!
- The first oil company
run for the people, by the people.
Think about finally having
everything you've always wished for.
- Let's go!
- [all laughing]
- [door opens]
- Hey!
[car horn honks]
[Maxwell] For a low monthly fee,
you can own a piece
of the most lucrative industry
in the world.
And every time we strike gold,
- you strike gold.
- [whoops] Oh!
[bride screaming]
[panting]
[Maxwell] No matter who you are,
no matter what you do,
you deserve to have it all.
Do you have everything
you've ever wanted?
Aren't you tired of
always wishing you had more?
- Hey, move it. It's my turn.
- Join me today.
- Yes!
- Operators are standing by.
You don't need a pile of money
or some business degree to get started.
You don't even have to work hard for it.
- [bell dinging]
- Good morning.
- Don't even think about it.
[Maxwell] At Black Gold Cooperative,
all you need
is to want it!
We get what we want, and we go.
- [saleswoman] What do you want?
- None of this junk.
Word is on the street
you got a nice little black market
side business going on back there.
If you don't tell, we won't tell.
- [laughing joyously]
- Yes, yes, yes!
[Buzz Cut] Oh, thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Yes, yes, yes!
[groans]
Sir, are you all right?
Gun!
- He's got a gun!
- [people screaming]
Shut up! Please!
Come on, dude. Can't hide.
Let's get out of here!
[security guard] Stop! Mall Security!
No, no, you, you, right there!
Right there! Freeze. Stop!
[Flat Top] Move, move, move!
Chief, they're running up the escalator.
Hey! Stop! Freeze!
Freeze!
[shopper] No!
- [woman yelps]
- [Buzz Cut panting]
[security guard] We have
several armed assailants running free.
We need the police here, right now.
[people screaming]
Freeze!
Freeze! Freeze!
Whoa, whoa! Hey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
No. Dude, dude, calm...
- Get back, man. I'll do it!
- [man 1 ] Hey!
Hey, what are you doing?
[Scowler] It's okay. It's gonna be okay.
- [man 1 ] What are you doing?
- [grunting]
- [girl screams]
- [shoppers gasp]
Hey, what are you doing?
- I'm not going back!
- No, no, no!
[panicked chattering]
[Scowler] Just chill out. Just chill.
- Stand back!
- Don't do it!
[man 2] No, no, no!
Put the kid back.
Listen to me.
- Listen to me!
- [all shout]
- No!
- What are you doing?
[Flat Top] Pull her back.
Pull her back in!
I'm not going back!
No!
Gonna let her go!
- No, no, no!
- No, no!
What? Who? What?
[grunts]
We won't be doing that today.
[sighs]
[gasps]
[screaming]
[Courtney whispers] Whoa.
We... We... We should go...
[Courtney] Oh, my gosh!
Hold tight.
[laughing]
[both screaming]
I hate guns.
We've got to go now. Come on.
[gasps]
[screaming]
[yelping]
- [coins clinking]
- [Scowler] Yo.
I'm sorry, lady.
- Shh.
- [Scowler] I'm sorry. Okay?
It was his idea.
- [sirens wailing]
- [people screaming]
[thieves groaning]
[reporter on TV] And the authorities
still have questions.
In fact, the first is a real doozy,
which is,
who exactly even stopped this crime?
If the story around here
is to be believed,
it wasn't the police,
but a mysterious female savior
that multiple witnesses saw.
If this sounds familiar, it should.
We've now had more than
a half-dozen similar sightings
across the greater D. C. area
in the last year.
Which, of course,
begs the biggest question of today,
who is this woman
and where did she come from?
[door closes]
[people laughing]
[waiter] Excuse me.
Are you waiting for someone?
No. Just me.
[sighs]
[man] Taxi!
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't see you there.
Hey, we could share, if you like?
No, thanks. I'll wait.
[airplane passing]
[objects clattering]
[gasps] Oh, my.
[male co-workers chattering]
- Yeah.
- [Barbara] Hey, Jake.
Jake, hi. Can you...
[male co-workers continue chattering]
Hi. [chuckles] I know, walk much?
The latch of my...
Good morning.
Hi. Thank you.
Diana Prince,
cultural anthropology and archaeology.
Barbara Minerva.
Geology, gemology, lithology,
and part-time cryptozoologist.
Oh, wow.
I kept busy in college.
Sorry. It's these heels, you know.
It's stupid.
I don't know why I was gonna wear heels.
Scientists don't wear heels.
- Sometimes we do.
- Right.
- Right. Those are cool!
- Have a nice day.
I like those.
Animal print. [growls]
[both laugh]
Do you want to get lunch?
I, uh...
Not now, obviously.
It's morning.
But later today, or whenever.
Like, around... Like, at lunchtime?
I have a lot of work today.
- But maybe some other time?
- Oh.
- Yeah, I'm busy today, too.
- Great.
Ah! Diana, do you happen to know
who a Barbara Minerva is?
[Barbara] Oh, hi, Carol. Hi.
It's me. I'm Barbara.
Remember? You hired me.
- Started last week.
- Oh!
Gemologist?
Yes. And zoologist.
- We had a couple interviews.
- Yeah.
Well, the FBI are gonna drop off
some artifacts later this afternoon.
[Barbara] The FBI?
- [Carol] Yeah. Yes.
- They're coming here?
The mall heist yesterday,
apparently they were using
a jewelry store as a front.
[Diana] Front for what?
Black market. Stolen jewels and art
meant for private buyers.
But we could use your help
identifying one in particular.
My help? [laughs]
Yeah, I'll help the FBI
with whatever they need.
Is that a yes?
Yes. I would, um...
- I would love to assist you.
- Wonderful.
It's nice to meet you.
We've met.
Have a nice day.
Bye, Diana.
[Barbara] Okay, item number 23.
[sighs] Shoot. That's not it.
Oh, the Empress of Siam.
Originally found in the wreck
of the Nuestra Señora de Atocha.
Wow.
Sorry. I couldn't resist coming to see.
Oh, it's okay.
Here it is.
- [Diana] What is it?
- Um...
Uh...
I can't tell.
Some light.
I think the technical term here
is "extremely lame."
[Barbara chuckles] Um...
It's... It's citrine.
A classic stone used in fakes
throughout history. [sighs]
I can't imagine this is worth
any more than $75.
What do you think?
Fakes aren't my forte, but let me see.
Mmm.
Latin.
[Barbara] At least
it's an antique, right?
Or a purchase from a stall
on the Ponte Vecchio last week.
- Mmm-hmm.
- You never know.
"Place upon the object held
but one great wish."
You read Latin?
Yeah. Yeah. Languages are a hobby.
So maybe it's, like, a lucky charm
or something?
Yeah, I guess.
Strange.
- I really wish I had a coffee.
- [Barbara laughs]
You're funny.
Hey, I got Erika a coffee, but she's
out sick. Does anybody want this?
[laughs] What? Yeah, I'll take one.
Ooh, hot!
- Hot, hot!
- [Barbara gasps]
Did you see that?
Oh...
Can you imagine?
- If only.
- Hmm.
So many things,
I don't even know what I would wish for.
I do.
[sighs]
Well, um, anyway, sorry to bother you.
If you need anything, I'm around.
- Oh, yeah, I'm good.
- Yeah.
But thank you for...
That's okay. It's my job.
And I'll look into it more
when I have a chance.
Okay.
Well, thanks for...
talking to me. [chuckles nervously]
I'm... I'm sorry, uh...
I mean, I'm fine.
[Diana] You know, we could go
and grab early dinner
and talk about exactly
how lame that stone is.
Really?
Yeah, I mean, citrine?
Who are they kidding, right?
- [laughing] So lame.
- Dorky.
- Lame.
- Yeah, let's go.
That's, like, the lamest of lames.
[watch ticking]
[Diana and Barbara laughing]
Wow. You're so funny.
- Oh. Thank you.
- Wow.
I mean, no one's made me laugh like this
in such a long time.
I mean, it's true,
I don't get out much socially.
You don't get out much?
No, not really.
- No.
- I'm sorry. I'm just surprised.
Because you just seem like
the kind of person
who's, like, always out.
Like, people are asking you
to go out all the time
and you live out. You're just out.
- [both laugh]
- Like, you never get in.
You just seem
like you'd be really popular.
And I would know
because I've never been popular.
You haven't?
You're so personable.
So... free.
I mean, honestly,
I gotta say that I envy that.
[laughing] What?
You envy me?
That doesn't make any sense.
Oh, my gosh.
People think I'm weird.
They avoid me
and talk behind my back
when they don't think I can hear them.
I'm like, "Guys, I can hear you."
[laughs nervously]
Barbara, my life
hasn't been
what you probably think it has.
We all have our struggles.
Yeah, we do.
Have you ever been in love?
Uh... Yeah.
- A long, long time ago.
- Mmm.
You?
So many times, yeah. All the time.
Often.
So what happened?
Where'd he go, your guy?
He, uh...
He died.
But I still think sometimes
that I see him up there in the sky.
He was a pilot.
- Oh!
- He was all kinds of things,
but he was great. It was true.
I get it.
Well, cheers to us.
Wishing us better luck, I guess.
Hey, Leon.
Hey there, Barbara. Late night?
Yeah. Going back to work.
I wanted to bring this to you
while it was still hot.
- Oh, you're too good to me.
- It's not a problem.
Stay warm.
[drunk man] Hey there, sweetheart.
You need some help?
No, I'm fine. Thank you.
'Cause, uh,
you know, you look as though
you're having a little bit of trouble
walking in those heels, huh?
It's okay.
I wear these heels all the time.
Hey, come on. Let me walk you home.
- I'm not going home.
- Hey, I'm just trying to be nice here.
Huh? Come on.
- Hey, hey. Hey, hey!
- [yelping]
- What are you doing?
- Hey, hey!
Let go of me!
- I'm just trying to help you!
- Let go of me! Let go of me!
[Barbara grunts] Let go!
[bin clattering]
- [drunk man groaning]
- [Barbara panting]
Forgot my keys. Lucky.
- How did you...
- Simple self-defense.
Used his own momentum against him.
I'll teach you.
Honestly, it takes no power at all.
Are you okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Good.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Go home, okay?
- Yeah.
- Good night.
I do know what I'd wish for.
To be like Diana.
- [wind whooshing]
- Strong, sexy,
cool.
Special.
[scoffs]
[watch ticking]
[door closes]
Oh...
[breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[janitor] Oh, no! Oh!
Sorry.
Oh, it's okay.
Barbara, thank God you're good in heels.
- Oh.
- [chuckles]
- Hey, Barbara.
- Hi, Jake.
Wow. [chuckles] Looking good.
- Oh, thanks.
- Yeah.
[Carol] This is our Earth Sciences lab.
Oh, Barbara!
Hi.
Perfect.
I have someone I would like you to meet.
- A pleasure, Ms. Minerva.
- Oh.
[chuckles] Uh, it's "Doctor," actually.
Um... Have we met before?
You look familiar.
- Do the thing. Do the thing.
- No.
Life is good, but it can be better.
- [gasps]
- [Carol laughing]
[Barbara] Oh, my gosh. From TV.
Oh, my gosh. You're the oil guy.
- "The oil guy." I'll take it.
- That's right.
[all laughing]
Mr. Lord is considering
becoming a Friend of the Smithsonian
at the Partner level.
- Oh.
- Which entitles him to a handful
of private tours of our facilities,
and he asked for you by name.
- Me?
- Well, what can I say, Doctor?
Your reputation precedes you.
And apparently we share a passion
for gemology.
- Wow, okay. We do.
- I'll leave you to it.
- Uh...
- [Maxwell chuckling]
Oh, let me just drop this off
in my office,
and we'll go.
Oh! Oh, gosh. Don't look in there.
It's such a mess.
So, I thought maybe
we could start upstairs.
[Maxwell and Barbara laughing]
[Barbara] I love that ruby.
Oh, no. Be careful with that.
- [Maxwell] What?
- [Barbara] That's very...
- [Maxwell imitates monster growling]
- [both laughing]
[Barbara] Hey, have you seen my friend?
Where'd he go?
- [Maxwell] I'm right here.
- [Barbara] You are.
- [Maxwell laughing]
- Thank God.
Oh, wait.
You've got a little dust on you.
- Sorry.
- [Diana] Hey, good morning.
Oh, hi.
- Hi.
- [Barbara] Oh! Uh...
This is the one and only,
Mr. Maxwell Lord.
It's him.
Life is good,
but it can be better.
[both laughing]
He's from TV.
Oh, I don't have a TV.
Well, I have a great relationship
with Sears.
I can get you a brand-new TV
by the end of the day.
Nineteen inches.
- No strings attached.
- I'll stick to the one I don't have.
But thank you.
Okay.
You're so generous. Um...
Headline... Uh...
Mr. Lord
took a tour of the entire Smithsonian
while considering partnership,
[giggles] and guess
what he decided to do?
Give his entire donation
to our department.
He's announcing it
at tonight's Members' Gala.
It's going to be an amazing party.
I hope you have something nice to wear.
I actually tend to skip these events.
I find that our benefactors
with a true eye towards philanthropy
prefer to stay out of the spotlight.
To let the museum's work
garner the attention.
I agree.
Except,
- I like to party.
- [laughing]
Oh, my gosh. You're such a good dancer.
- You like Latin dancing?
- I love it.
I know that I'm a terrible dancer.
No, I doubt
that you're a terrible dancer...
No, I've got a hip injury
from high school.
...the shape that you're in.
[Diana] Great, so,
- thank you so much for coming.
- [Barbara] Oh, yeah.
[Maxwell] You know,
I really should be going.
Thank you for the tour.
I will have to see you tonight.
See you tonight. [laughs]
Bye. Have a good day.
I'll find you.
What?
I like him.
[Barbara laughs]
[Maxwell] Thank you, John.
[Maxwell grunts]
[Maxwell chattering indistinctly
on recording]
Ladies.
Mr. Lord.
Not now, Raquel. My supplements?
[Raquel] On your desk, but Mr. Lord.
Mr. Lord.
[elevator bell dings]
[sighs]
[running footsteps approaching]
[Raquel] Mr. Lord.
[panting] Mr. Lord.
[Alistair] Dad!
[Maxwell] How?
How!
It's your weekend.
Yes, clearly.
Alistair. [chuckles]
Where's the pool, Daddy?
It's not done yet, buddy.
But it doesn't matter.
[sighs] You just have to be patient.
I told you the pool,
the helicopter,
you'll have it all.
But remember,
Rome wasn't built in a day, was it? No.
[Alistair] Hasn't it been a lot of days?
Well, it takes time
to become a great, great,
number-one man,
like your dad is going to be.
[Stagg] Are you lying to your son,
like you lie to everyone else?
[coughing]
Simon.
[Maxwell hesitates]
These offices aren't ready
for guests yet.
- [Maxwell chuckles]
- It's over, Max.
I don't want to hear it anymore.
I'm out.
Alistair, go wait with Raquel.
Simon.
I know it's hard to see right now,
but we are finally right at the edge
of turning this thing around.
"Turning it around"?
There is no oil. There never was.
So how are you gonna turn it around?
[scoffs] Get more sucker investors,
like me?
- It's called a Ponzi scheme.
- No!
I have a big... [sighs heavily]
There's something in the works.
And it's no scheme.
Simon, we have millions of acres
of potentially oil-rich land.
You have oil rights on land
that everyone else passed on already.
Now, it didn't take much digging
to find that out.
I should have
done some digging on you, too,
Maxwell Lorenzano.
Didn't take long to find out
you're nothing but a lowlife con man.
I am not a con man!
- I am a television personality.
- [groans]
And a respected businessman
- with a plan.
- Come on.
- With... With... With a great plan.
- Oh!
"If you can dream it, you can have it."
Something like that?
You have 48 hours
- to get my money...
- You're going to regret this.
- ...or the FTC gets an anonymous report.
- [forced laughing]
- Loser.
- Simon, wait.
Simon, wait.
[yells in frustration]
I am not a loser.
He's a loser!
And don't you ever believe
a word that man said.
He's a liar...
and he's wrong.
[sighs]
And he will rue the day
he walked away from me.
And you...
You are going to be so proud
to be my son.
Okay.
You'll see.
Everyone will.
[saleswoman]
These are known for a terrific fit.
[Barbara] Yeah,
I'm just not so great with heels.
Just try them.
- Come out and show me.
- [Barbara sighs]
[Barbara] Okay. Hmm.
They do fit well.
Ah.
[Barbara] Huh.
- Yeah, I like it.
- [saleswoman] You look
amazing.
Do you think it's too tight?
I think it's just right.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
I'll take it.
[indistinct chattering]
['80s pop music playing]
Hey there. How are you doing?
The animals are winding me up
The jungle call
Who-ha! Who-ha! Who-ha! Who-ha!
In Xanadu did Kublai Khan
A pleasure dome erect...
[men laughing]
- Those shoes are incredible.
- Thank you.
- What a beautiful dress.
- You look fantastic.
[chuckles] Thank you so much.
Dr. Minerva.
[sighs]
[laughs] You look breathtaking.
Thank you.
I... You know, we have to go to
these sort of things for work a lot,
so I've probably worn this dress
a million times.
Mmm.
Um...
Actually, no. [laughs nervously] I...
I just bought this today.
I never look like this.
Um, not even close.
Took me a long time to get ready.
Biotin.
You should try it.
Makes you glow like a teenager.
Reverses the clock.
Never accept the limitations of nature.
Yeah, no.
Especially not a beautiful woman
like you.
[Barbara chuckling] Oh...
God, it's so loud in here.
Yeah.
Can we go somewhere?
- Just me and you?
- Yes.
Hmm... Your office?
[Barbara chuckles nervously]
[both moaning]
Oh, wow! Look at all of this stuff.
It's so...
It's so beautiful.
Like you.
[both chuckling]
What is that?
Um...
Uh, it's nothing special, really.
But the FBI did ask me
to help them identify it.
[Maxwell] Wow.
[Barbara] Though it certainly
has me stumped so far.
Let me help you.
Max is here.
No need to be stumped ever again.
I have a dear friend
in Roman antiquities.
- Roman antiquities.
- Could give it a look, if you like?
[Barbara giggles]
It is Latin, isn't it?
[Barbara breathing heavily]
I really shouldn't let it
go out of the museum.
[both moaning]
- Hey there, beautiful.
- No, thank you. Excuse me.
[Carl] Oh, Diana.
Hoping I'd see you.
Hey, do you know
I'm at the White House now?
Yeah, that's right.
Interning, but requested by name, so...
Listen, I've had my eyes on you
for some time.
- So if you ever need...
- That's great, Carl.
Diana.
Excuse me, I don't even know you,
so please stop following me.
- Good night.
- But... [sighs]
I wish we had more time.
Why did you say that?
Don't say that to me.
You don't even know me.
Yes, I do.
I can save today...
but you can save the world.
Steve?
Diana.
But how?
I don't know.
[mouthing] Oh, my God.
It's you.
I missed you.
[Diana] So what do you remember?
[Steve] I remember...
I remember taking the plane up...
[Diana] Mmm-hmm.
...and then...
nothing, really.
Nothing.
But somehow,
I know I've been some place since then.
Some place that's, uh...
I can't really put words to it.
But it's... It's good.
And then I, uh... I woke up here.
Where?
I ended up in a bed. Uh...
Strange, strange pillow bed with slats.
- A futon, yeah.
- A futon?
- Yeah.
Well, not comfortable.
And really a bit backwards
if I'm being really honest with you.
I mean, for a futuristic time like this.
Nineteen...
Eighty-four. 1984.
[both sigh]
[airplane passing]
[Steve] That's amazing.
[Steve chuckles in astonishment]
[Diana laughing joyously]
[Steve] Would you like to see my futon?
- [kicks]
- [door closes]
- [objects clattering]
- [Diana gasps]
Yeah. Um...
You don't have to tell me.
The place is a mess. Cheese on demand.
I spent all morning
cleaning his bedroom,
but he seems to me to be an engineer.
Lots of pictures of himself.
Not what I would do,
but to each his own.
Oh, so this is how you found me.
Yeah, the phone book.
I guess some things
are just future-proof.
So you went to my apartment?
Yeah, I tried to use the bike at first.
I couldn't really figure out
how to get it going,
so I ran over and saw you come back.
And I was stunned.
There you were.
So I just, uh...
followed you, like a creep.
Diana, look at you. It's...
It's like not one day has passed.
I can't say the same thing about you.
[sighs] Right, right, right. Right.
Yeah, he's, uh...
He's got it.
[laughing] No, I like him.
He's great, but all I see is you.
"One great wish." I've been waiting.
I wish to be you.
The Dreamstone itself.
[wind whooshing]
[groaning]
[laughing]
[sighs]
[gasps]
Hi.
Come here.
- Good morning.
[Diana hums happily]
Been eating Pop-Tarts all morning,
and I've had about three pots of coffee.
This place is amazing. [laughing]
- This place?
- Yeah.
You know, if I really think about it,
I don't think I've ever been in a room
more amazing.
- It's true.
- Yeah.
This room is the most amazing place
- I've ever been in, in my entire life.
- It's the most amazing place, right?
So let's stay. We shouldn't go.
- I really don't want to.
- So, let's not.
- Okay.
Let's just stay here.
[Diana] Forever.
Although...
I should probably go and figure out
how a stone brought my boyfriend back
in someone else's body.
- [Steve breathing heavily]
- [Diana humming]
That's a fair point. Let's go.
[replaces barbell]
Whoa.
- [computer beeps]
- [knocking on door]
[Belinda] Mr. Stagg?
Thank you, Belinda.
Oh, God.
You'd better be here with my money.
I'll have your money, Simon.
Today, I'm here for an apology.
Are you out of your mind?
I'm not going to apologize.
I'm sorry.
I messed up. I messed up.
I lied.
And I'm sorry.
You know, the truth is, I knew
we were going to sink a long time ago.
The wells were coming up dry.
And no data suggested
that was going to change.
I should have folded then.
But all the people that bought in,
that believed in me.
- I wanted to do right.
- Oh, come on.
Max, look, you don't have to...
Simon, don't you understand
that I wished for better?
That with every ounce of my being,
I wished that Black Gold
would change the world for all of us.
And I know you wished that, too.
- Of course I wished that, too.
- [wind whooshing]
Then your wish is granted.
And in return,
I'll take all of your shares...
and full control of Black Gold,
after you are somehow
magically removed from my path...
- You're gonna what?
- ...forever.
[Stagg] Max!
Hey, Max!
- Get back here! Max!
- Ow.
What the hell is going on?
[tires screeching]
We have a warrant for Simon Stagg.
My word. Are we in danger?
No, sir. Federal taxation crime.
It doesn't concern you. Move along.
[guard] Send them through.
- [man] Okay. Follow me.
- [agent] Let's go, guys.
[spraying]
[sniffing]
Ooh.
- [continues spraying]
- [laughs]
So you said a stone started all of this?
Yeah, that's what we need
to go and find out.
I mean, it must have done something.
- This is dynamite.
- [Diana sighs]
What do you think?
- Yeah. Yeah...
- Huh? Right?
I saw a couple of magazine pictures.
They roll these up.
I think we can do better.
Look at all the pockets in this.
There are pockets here.
There are pockets all over the pant.
American issue bag, adjustable.
Parachute pants?
- Yeah. Uh...
- Does everybody parachute now?
You know, I'm not so keen on this one.
I figure you are, but you know what,
I'm ready to go.
[Diana] Mmm-mmm.
- Right?
- No.
- You're not even giving it a second.
- It's not good.
"Too much" in a good way or a bad way?
Right?
- In a bad way.
- Oh.
Now that's great.
It's beautiful.
Yeah. I would absolutely never wear it.
- I feel like a pirate.
- Steve.
Who would wear this?
Diana,
have you seen these shoes?
- Let's keep the shoes.
- Let's keep the shoes. Yes!
- Yes!
[Diana] This is a special one, okay?
- Let's do this together.
- Uh-huh.
One foot after the other.
Now stay on this one.
Go to the middle.
No, Steve...
- Steve, you're gonna fall.
- [yelps]
[Steve laughing]
I really thought I was gonna fall.
[indistinct chattering]
What's up?
[subway train approaching]
[hip-hop music playing on stereo]
This is break dance.
- [Steve] Dancing?
- [Diana] Yeah.
[Steve laughing]
- Whoa!
- Oh, don't worry.
- It's fine. It's just a move.
- Yeah? Oh.
It's nothing.
It's all art.
Yeah.
Uh... That's just a trash can.
It's just a trash can.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is that a plane?
Come on. I want to show you something.
[announcer chattering on PA]
[Diana chuckling]
[Steve gasps]
This is incredible! [laughing]
[Maxwell on recording]
And every time we strike gold,
- you strike gold.
- [phone ringing]
Think about finally having
everything you've always wished for.
Raquel?
- Raquel?
- [phone continues ringing]
- [ringing]
- Black Gold. Can you hold, please?
[phones ringing continuously]
Black Gold. Yes. Hold, please.
- Raquel?
- Hold, please.
The wells struck pay!
- Which ones?
- All of them.
And the investors
heard about it somehow.
They're calling to up their buys.
Their friends are calling to buy in.
New investors are calling
out of thin air.
Hold on, please.
I need more help.
- Black Gold. Can you hold, please?
- I'll get you help.
Tell me again.
You wish you had more help?
- Yes, I wish I had more help.
- [wind whooshing]
There are just too many calls to take.
[Emerson] Uh... Hi.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm meant to be interviewing
at an accounting firm.
- You're hired!
- [Emerson] Oh...
Welcome aboard!
- Emerson.
- Emerson!
Is this the employment office?
Yes! You're hired, too!
Mr. Lord, it's Wall Street Journal.
They want to interview you
about company's sudden surge.
I'll take it in my office.
And bring me my vitamins.
So I did read
about four books last night...
[all laughing]
...to try to get to the bottom of this.
And did find out, Roger, you were right.
This is from the Song Dynasty.
You were correct.
And also interesting,
I was looking at a couple
of encyclopedias last night and you...
Thanks. Um...
[laughs]
So funny, all this reading seems
to have cured my eyesight somehow.
[all laughing]
- Interesting fact which we...
- Hey.
- Hi.
- [Diana] Good morning.
This is Steve. He's my, um...
- Old friend.
- Yeah.
Hi, old friend Steve. [laughs]
I'm Barbara, Diana's new friend.
So what do you do?
I'm a pilot.
- Pilot? Isn't that...
- Can I speak to you for a second?
Sure.
So, I just wanted to speak to you
about that stone.
The citrine one.
[hesitating]
- Do you have it?
- Uh...
Long story, actually, about that.
Max Lord came by to visit yesterday.
Which was actually pretty great.
I'll tell you about it later. Um...
I let him
borrow it.
What? Why?
Well, Diana,
he just gave us a huge amount of money.
It's not like he's a stranger
or anything.
Plus he has a friend who's an expert,
and I don't know...
What do you mean? How could you loan it?
- It's not even ours to loan.
- Whoa. Whoa.
What are you getting on my case for?
I've got 15 things in my office
more valuable than that stone.
Do you know where he took it?
No, I have no idea.
Then I'll tell you what we find out.
Let's go.
- I like your pants very much.
- Oh, thanks.
Yeah. Call me.
Or not. Whatever.
But I'd be curious.
[police siren wails]
[man on PA] Call the Black Gold hotline.
Shares are not available
in the building.
What are these people doing?
Whatever it is,
we're not getting in that way.
Diana. Diana, this way.
Have at it.
[grunts]
Strong lock.
- [phones ringing continuously]
- [people chattering]
[whispers] Steve.
[Diana blowing]
- It's so dusty.
- Yeah.
It's like a bomb went off.
[Steve] Whatever this is, he's been
looking for it for a long time.
[Diana] "Place upon the object held."
[gasps]
What is it?
[breathing heavily]
The language of the Gods.
Which God wrote it, is the question.
- [phone ringing]
- Thanks.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah. It's okay.
I gotta go do something. Okay.
I'll talk to you. All right?
- Hello?
- [Diana] Barbara, I need your help.
I need you to find out
exactly where that stone was found.
"Where" is what I need to know.
You understand?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I'm on it.
Thanks.
You look like you saw a ghost.
I did.
There were many Gods
and they did different things
for different reasons.
One was making objects like this.
There are universal elements
in this world,
and when they're imbued into something,
they can become very, very powerful.
Like my Lasso of Truth.
The truth is what powers it, not me.
The truth is bigger than all of us.
But what is this?
I don't know. Uh...
Brought me back.
Love or hope...
maybe?
[Diana] Maybe.
Well, whatever it is, I can promise you
this is too powerful for Maxwell Lord.
We need to find this guy.
Uh...
Look at this.
If this date's right,
he's going to Cairo.
Cairo?
[Steve] Yeah.
Growth opportunity, you know?
[Diana] "King of Crude"?
How is this so fast?
You have a plane that can fly
from here to Cairo in one shot?
That is amazing. [laughs]
Yeah, but we can't get you on one
because you don't have a passport.
I don't want to get on one,
I want to fly one.
I want to fly the plane.
I want to fly this plane.
Yeah?
- [keypad buzzes]
- [doors unlock]
[Steve] Oh, my Betsy.
[Diana] Hey, Steve, this way.
Yeah.
Look at these gams.
[Steve gasping]
You wanna choose?
This one.
[Diana] I like it.
[Steve grunts]
Okay.
Okay. Uh...
No.
Uh...
[Steve laughs]
All right. Good, good.
Fuel, fuel, fuel.
Here we go. Engine.
[engine starting]
Here goes nothing.
Oh...
[Steve laughing in delight]
[beeping]
- Ken?
- [Ken] What?
There's an aircraft on the runway.
What do you mean,
"There's an aircraft on the runway"?
Approach, this is Tower.
There's an unlisted aircraft
on the runway.
Are you seeing this?
[siren wailing]
- Can you get us up there?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just have to pick up speed first,
and then I'll take off.
The way I fly, they will never find us.
[soldiers shouting]
- Oh, I forgot to tell you.
- What?
Radar. I can't explain now,
but they'll see us anywhere,
even in the dark.
Well, will they shoot at us?
- Well, shit, Diana.
- [mouthing] Right.
[sirens wailing]
- [mouthing] Diana.
- Wait. Shh! I know.
I know. [exhales deeply] Focus.
Focus.
My father hid Themyscira from the world,
and I've been trying to learn
how he did it.
Did what?
Made something invisible.
But in 50 years, I've only done it once.
Well, now's not a bad time
to start trying.
- How long does it last?
- I don't know.
It was just a coffee cup...
and I lost it.
[shouting]
[breathing deeply]
[yelling]
[air traffic controller] Approach,
the aircraft has vanished.
Do you have eyes on it?
[Diana laughing]
[Steve exhales deeply]
An invisible jet.
[Steve laughing]
[muffled bursting]
What's that?
[Diana] Oh, it's okay.
It's just fireworks.
The Fourth. Of course.
The Fourth of July?
Wow.
[Diana laughs]
I got an idea.
[Diana exhales]
[both laughing]
[breathing heavily]
You know, it's the one thing.
The one thing
that's always been you to me.
What?
Flight.
Your gift.
I'll never understand it.
Ah, it's...
It's so easy, really.
It's wind and air
and knowing how to ride it,
how to catch it.
How to join with it.
Yeah.
It's like anything, really.
[agent] Great, thanks.
Found the last one.
This should keep you busy for a while.
Anything else I can get you? Coffee?
Tea?
Me?
I don't need anything from you,
and I'm done.
You're done?
Hey, you don't have to be mean about it.
[man] Hey, babe. Where you going?
[panting] No thanks.
Ooh, you're pretty.
Hey, slow down, sexy.
You talking to me?
Yep. I'm talking to you.
Why don't you just slow down a bit, huh?
Come on, girl.
I'd rather not. You know what I mean?
I'd rather not have anything to do
with someone like you.
I'd rather you stop harassing people.
Like me.
Do you remember me?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I remember. Where were we, huh?
No.
[breathing heavily]
[groaning]
[drunk man] No.
[Barbara] She's right.
It's not that hard.
[Barbara grunts]
Yeah, I think I get it now.
His body weight does do all the work.
So easy.
I think
I could do this...
[whimpering]
- All...
- [groaning]
night...
long!
[continues groaning]
[Leon] Barbara?
What are you doing?
Mind your business.
Sir?
[Emir] Your fortune the last few days
has been impressive, to say the least.
But why come all this way
to meet with me? Hmm?
[Maxwell] To meet a peer.
[Emir] A peer?
No, Mr. Lord. I only agreed
to meet with you because I was curious.
No one gets that lucky.
How did you do it?
On my journey to self-fulfillment...
I lucked into a secret.
[whispering] The secret of the wish.
So I wished for it.
Or someone wished for it for me.
Tell me what you wish for,
Your Highness,
and I will show you how it works.
I wish for things one cannot attain.
Like what?
All of my land to be returned.
My ancestral realm.
The Bialyian Dynasty.
And for all the heathens
who dare trod upon it
to be kept out forever,
so that its glory may be renewed.
You wish for that?
I wish for that deeply.
[wind whooshing]
Your wish is granted.
And in return, I will take your oil.
[Emir laughing]
You truly delight me.
You know so little.
I sold my oil to the Saudis.
You are a silly man.
[continues laughing]
[all laughing]
Then I will take your security team
and leave you here
with nothing to defend yourself
against the wrath you most
certainly will face. [snaps fingers]
[guard shouting in Arabic]
[head guard speaking Arabic]
[Emir's aide speaking Arabic]
[all speaking Arabic]
[people clamoring]
[in English] Stop! Stop the car!
What are you doing?
Stop what you're doing now!
I'm telling you.
I command you to stop!
Stop!
Stop! Stop!
[news anchor on TV]
This unbelievable and unexplainable wall
appears to somehow be the work
of Emir Said Bin Abydos.
The government is reporting
old rulings have emerged
acknowledging his claim to the land.
You okay?
I'm fine.
- You keep saying that, but...
- [jeep horn honking]
That was him!
That was Max Lord.
[speaking Arabic]
[tires screeching]
[in English] Get rid of them, please.
[speaking Arabic]
[tires screeching]
[in English] I got this.
What?
Diana!
[Wonder Woman grunts]
The brakes still work.
[tires screeching]
[gasps]
[panting]
[guard shouting in Arabic]
[yelps]
[grunting]
[panting]
[Steve grunts]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[in English] Max Lord,
you're putting yourself
and everyone else in grave danger.
I need you to give me the stone.
What happened to it?
You're looking at it.
[Maxwell laughs]
Whoa!
[grunting]
[groans]
[yelps]
[continues grunting]
[straining]
[yelps]
[Wonder Woman grunts]
Steve!
Diana!
[straining]
[Wonder Woman panting]
So who's the next closest person
with oil?
[Wonder Woman speaking Arabic]
[groans]
- [people chattering]
- [Wonder Woman groaning]
[in English] Diana. Diana.
My God. What's going on with you?
[news anchor 1 ]
A truly bizarre phenomenon
- that is being called the Divine Wall.
- [Wonder Woman] What is happening?
[news anchor 1 ]
It's an unexplainable event
that now sees
Egypt's poorest communities
entirely cut off from their only supply
of fresh water.
[news anchor 2] An already
tense situation now escalating
as the Soviet Union announces
they will recognize the Emir's claim.
- Oh, no.
- The United States,
a longtime ally of Egypt, has declared
their intention to side
with the government.
Bedlam on the home front now as well
as the shocking news
that American businessman
Max Lord has somehow
come into possession
of over half
of the world's oil reserves.
The instability in the oil community
has resulted
in a nationwide run on gas,
- and experts are girding themselves...
- [phone ringing]
Hello?
Barbara, it's Diana.
- Did you...
- Yeah. Uh, well, sort of.
I haven't figured out
exactly what the stone is,
but I've found historical images of it.
From where?
That's the weird thing.
From everywhere.
It first appeared in the Indus Valley
almost 4,000 years ago.
It popped up again
in Carthage in 146 BC.
Kush, 4 AD.
Romulus, the last Emperor of Rome,
he had it on him
when he was assassinated in 476.
The last record is
in some previously unknown dead city
near Dzibilchaltun.
- The Mayans.
- Yeah.
Anyway, it just led me
to a bunch of dead ends,
and my last lead is not that promising.
What's that?
A flyer I found.
Grabbed it at the embassy.
Some guy advertising
to be a Mayan shaman.
But he literally teaches a course
in a squat next to Galaxy Records.
- And he knows about the stone?
- So he says.
I'm gonna go there in the morning.
Okay, we'll meet you there.
And thank you.
[Steve] What is it?
The stone has traveled the world
to seemingly random
and different places,
- but they all have one thing in common.
- What?
Their civilizations collapsed
catastrophically.
Without a trace as to why.
You don't think the stone could have...
Do you?
I don't know what to think, Steve.
I can only hope I'm wrong.
[wind howling]
[Babajide coughing]
Babajide?
- That was fast.
- Morning.
Hello.
One second.
[Babajide sighs]
- So you're a Mayan?
- [Babajide humming]
What? I'm a citizen of the world.
It says your name is Frank.
Yeah. Most of what I know
is a past-life thing.
So that's a no.
[Babajide] But to answer
your question, yes.
My great-great-grandfather
left me this.
I don't know everything about it,
but I have been warned
I'm better off that way.
What I do know is,
it destroyed our people
in a matter of months.
The few survivors,
they buried the stone,
never to be exhumed
under any circumstances.
- [Diana] Can I see that?
- [Babajide] Be my guest.
[Diana gasps]
[Steve] What?
What is it?
[Diana] Dechalafrea Ero.
[Steve] What's that?
A very bad God.
The God of Lies, Dolos, Mendacius,
Duke of Deception.
He's been called by many names.
But if he's the one
who empowered that stone,
there has to be a trick.
What do lies have to do
with granting wishes?
It seems more like a Dreamstone to me.
Wishes with a trick.
"The Monkey's Paw."
Beware what you wish for.
It grants your wish,
but takes your most valued possession.
Diana, your powers.
[Barbara] No, that doesn't
make any sense.
What's more precious
than what you wish for?
How do we stop this?
[Babajide] The legend said
it can only be stopped
by destroying the stone itself
or give back what was given.
My people couldn't do the first thing
and refused to do the second.
Now the culture's destroyed.
Wiped from the face of the Earth.
- No one renounced their wish?
- But the stone is already destroyed.
What? When?
[whispers] "You're looking at it."
"You're looking at it."
That's what Max Lord said to me.
Maybe it's him.
He's become it somehow.
[Steve] But how would that happen?
I mean, if he wished for...
No, that's crazy. No.
[Steve] If we destroy it,
if we destroy him...
all the wishes go back.
[Barbara] What are you
talking about? No.
I'm not gonna be a part of that. No.
Or if everyone renounces their wish.
[Barbara] No, there has to be
a better way.
No.
She's right.
We don't know enough.
We just don't know enough.
But what we do know is that we need
to stop him before he grants any more.
Stopping him might not be enough, Diana.
Wishes have been made.
Barbara?
[indistinct chattering]
[Maxwell] Like I want any of these
people in the club anyway.
Can we tell them they're not invited?
No, sir.
- The FCC said we couldn't...
- Oh, the FCC.
The BBB, the FBD.
It's a conspiracy against my success.
They're jealous. That's why.
Who's next?
- Who's next?
- Well, everyone you asked for,
Lai Zhong, Mr. Khalaji,
- that televangelist who stole your slot.
- Mmm.
And you have Alistair for the night.
Alistair? Again?
How many weekends do I have?
What? What? When?
Tonight?
[Emerson] He's here already.
His mom is with her boyfriend.
[Maxwell sighs heavily]
Send in Mr. Zhong, please.
And buy Alistair a pony.
No! A race car.
Get him a race car.
Let's get to it, Lai.
Tell me...
what do you want?
What do you wish for?
- Me? Truly?
- Mmm-hmm.
Mmm-hmm.
The Soviets have sided with Iran.
Iraq is preparing to defend ourselves,
as unrest spreads.
And you need? What do you...
What do you wish for?
Consider the sex tape gone.
And God darn it,
if I have to keep doing this
one by one, by one, by one...
- How's your health?
- Well...
Forget that.
But I will take your entire congregation
and your time slot.
Let me ask you,
when they pray, is there any way
I could get all of them to...
join hands with me?
And simply say, "I wish"
rather than, "I pray"?
Would that even work?
I don't...
I need to find a way
to touch a lot of people
at the same time.
[knocking on door]
Sir. The police are here.
They're challenging the jurisdiction
of your security team.
[Maxwell] Oh, God! [bangs table]
This isn't working.
Bring in someone new.
And my son.
You, beat it.
[Maxwell coughing]
- [clearing throat]
- [knocking on door]
Alistair!
[door closes]
I've missed you, buddy.
Come. Sit down with Daddy. I'm sorry.
But, your dad is
on the absolute precipice of everything.
Remember when I told you
that I would be number one?
Do you remember? Your dad?
Well, I'm inches away. Huh?
I know it's hard. I know.
But listen,
I also know what you wish for,
and I wish for it, too.
Do you hear that? I wish for it, too.
I just wish I could be with you...
No!
You don't use
your one wish like that, Alistair.
You don't wish for
something that you already have.
You wish for greatness, for success.
That's why I'm doing all of this.
Don't you see that my greatness
is your greatness? Huh?
Then I wish for your greatness.
- [wind whooshing]
- No. No!
Thank you.
I love you so much.
And I promise you, one day,
everything is going to make sense.
And one day, you'll thank me.
But right now, I, uh...
Right now, I need you to stay here
with Emerson, okay? I'll be back.
You stay here.
[door closes]
[indistinct chattering]
You. You.
Yes, sir?
Don't you wish I had an audience
with the President today?
Of course I do.
And can I tell you how happy I am
that you value my opinion, sir.
Wait a minute.
Have I asked for your wish before?
Yesterday. A Porsche.
What is it with you aides and Porsches?
You!
Hi.
- This way.
- [crowd clamoring]
How's traffic?
Huh? Terrible.
Don't you wish it wasn't?
And that everywhere you went
parted like the great Red Sea?
Of course I wish that.
Sadly, ain't gonna happen.
[officer] Hey, you! Stop!
Come on in. It's not safe.
There's a riot at the Saudi Embassy
and there are Porsches
racing up and down the street.
Come on. It's mad.
- But my cows.
- [cows mooing]
I told a man I wanted a farm.
I didn't mean here.
I'll be right back.
[sirens wailing in distance]
[watch ticking]
- Diana, I know it's been hard.
- [scoffs]
You don't know. You don't.
But we...
It can't go on like this.
- I can't talk about this.
- We have to talk about it.
Steve, I can't talk about this!
I give everything I have, every day.
And I'm happy to.
But this one thing...
You're all that I've wanted for so long.
You're the only joy I've had
or even asked for.
I am so sorry...
but that's crazy. [hesitates]
There's a world out there full of
so many better guys, for one.
I mean, how about this guy?
How about him?
I don't want him. I want you.
Why, for once,
can't I just have this one thing, Steve?
This one thing.
I'm not sure we have a choice.
Well, I do have a choice.
And I can't give you up. I can't.
So I won't. So we need to stop him
so we can figure that out.
There has to be another way.
Has to.
[indistinct chatter on TV]
Wow.
This is incredible.
What's that?
From my culture.
The armor of an ancient Amazon warrior.
One of our greatest.
It's huge. This whole thing?
What is it made out of?
Here. Let me show you.
Give me your hand.
What are you talking about?
I haven't lied.
The Lasso does more
than just make you tell the truth.
It can make you see it, too.
[sighs]
[Diana] Her name was Asteria.
She was our greatest warrior.
When mankind enslaved the Amazons,
my mother freed us.
But someone had to stay behind
to hold back the tide of men
so the others
could escape to Themyscira.
My people gave up all of their armor
to make her one suit strong enough
to take on the whole world.
And Asteria sacrificed herself
for a better day for others.
[breathing heavily]
[Steve] That's...
That's incredible.
When I came here, I searched for her.
But all I could find was her armor.
What is this?
[Steve] Where is he going?
[Diana] Oh, no.
Diana, Diana! What are you doing?
- Where are you going?
- Steve, I'm going. You need to stay.
No. No. Listen to me.
You're getting weaker, Diana.
- What if you fall?
- I won't.
You might. We don't know that.
There has to be another way in.
Everything okay, Mr. President?
Yes.
Something very strange. I...
I thought I was somewhere else entirely.
Suddenly...
Anyway. Hectic times.
Give us a minute.
[Diana] Excuse me.
- Carl.
- Diana.
- Hi.
- What a pleasure.
Good to see you. How have you been?
- Good.
- This is Steve.
Steve, this is Carl. My colleague.
- Hi.
Shall we, uh...
Yeah, we shall.
I'm sorry, Mr. Lord.
In fact, I don't even know
what we're supposed to discuss.
Exactly that, Mr. President.
These hectic days, hectic times.
And you.
[Carl] These aren't exactly my favorite
of the busts on display here,
but it's a little picture of my top ten,
maybe top five at a push.
Oh, here's something up ahead
that will interest you.
These are floor tiles originally laid
by none other than Jan Lincoln,
a little-known descendent of Abraham.
You're having some troubles?
Everywhere suddenly.
Cuba, Egypt,
even here.
But Russia...
- very troublesome.
- Mmm.
I appreciate your concern,
but all the money in the world
won't help us now.
It's not money I'm offering.
You.
You are a man of faith,
and I have been very blessed lately.
I want to share my blessing with you.
The power of positive thinking.
Now...
tell me, Mr. President,
what do you need?
And you're not speaking to me here,
but to the universe.
What do you wish for?
- What is there to wish for but more?
- [wind whooshing]
More nuclear weapons.
More than they have.
Closer to 'em.
If I just had that in place,
then they would have to listen to us.
[laughing] A nice thought.
And I grant you...
[groaning]
Oh... Oh, my...
[Maxwell continues groaning]
[breathing heavily]
And you know what I'd like?
I would want all of your power,
influence, authority.
All the respect you command
and the command everyone must respect.
[Maxwell groaning]
[laughing]
I mean, what else is there?
Now, tell your people I would appreciate
absolutely no interference whatsoever.
No taxes, no rule of law, no limits.
Treat me like a foreign nation
with absolute autonomy.
Very good, sir.
Right away.
What's this?
[POTUS] Global Broadcast Satellite.
Top-secret program that enables us
to override any broadcast system
in the world
in case we need direct contact
with the people of an enemy state.
So what does that mean?
You're taking over everyone's TVs?
How?
[POTUS] It uses
particle beam technology,
just like the Star Wars program.
Apparently, it bathes the landscape
in a signal of particles that goes in
and fiddles with
any technology it touches.
New or old. Broadcast whatever you want.
Very impressive.
You said "touches"?
As in the particles you are sending...
are touching everything?
[POTUS] It's a figure of speech,
but yes.
- That's how it was explained to me.
- I need immediate access
to this satellite. And a chopper
to get me there.
-Yes, sir. Right away. [snaps fingers]
[grunts]
Well, aren't you resourceful?
Come with me
before you do any more damage, Max.
No. I don't think so.
Remove this woman, please...
- permanently.
- [Wonder Woman grunts]
[groans]
[both groan]
- Are you okay?
- I don't know.
No, Steve. You can't use that.
- It's not their fault.
- [Steve panting]
[sword clatters]
[grunts]
[groans]
[both grunting]
That's neat.
[whimpering]
[both groaning]
Barbara.
I can't let you do this, Diana.
[Wonder Woman groaning]
[Steve grunting]
Barbara. What...
- How...
- I can't let you stop Max.
You're not the only one
with something to lose.
Turns out wishing to be like you...
came with some surprises.
[guard 1 ] Hands up.
- Hands up.
- [guard 1 ] Hands up, hands up.
[guard 2] Hands up!
- Hands up!
- [guard 1 ] Now! Now, now!
[all grunting]
[guard 3 screaming]
[guard 4] Open fire!
[groans]
[screaming]
Oh, how sweet, defending your love. Huh?
What do you wish for?
Do you wanna be a real boy?
No.
Just not to be handcuffed to you,
but now I am.
[both grunting]
- I just learned that.
- [both chuckling]
[both grunting]
[groans]
[all grunting]
[Wonder Woman] Barbara, stop!
Ahh!
[groaning]
[both grunt]
Listen.
You have no idea
what you're dealing with.
I'm not what you think.
You can't possibly
understand or handle...
Oh, I can't possibly understand?
[both grunting]
Oh...
Dumb little old me.
Dumb little, poor little
nothing, nobody me.
I couldn't possibly handle it.
No, Barbara. That's not what I'm saying.
Well, I'm handling it beautifully.
And I'm not giving it back!
[all grunting]
[groans]
[panting]
Go.
Run!
Everyone, stand down.
Nobody hurts her.
They couldn't if they tried.
[breathing heavily]
[groaning]
[Barbara] You've always had everything,
while people like me have had nothing.
Well, now it's my turn.
And you are not taking it from me. Ever!
But what is it costing you?
What is it costing me?
If it's the monkey's paw,
it takes as much as it gives.
Yes, you're strong...
but what did you lose, Barbara?
Where's your warmth, your joy,
your humanity?
You're attacking innocent men, Barbara.
Look at yourself.
Forget about me.
What is it costing you?
Yeah, yeah.
That's right.
Get used to it.
If you go after Max Lord...
or hurt him in any way,
I will destroy you.
Barbara!
[Steve yelps]
[groaning]
[Steve panting]
Are you all right?
- [Steve grunts]
- [Wonder Woman groaning]
[breathing heavily]
[door opens]
Room for one more?
[White House staffer]
Sir, you need to wait.
- The President has a meeting right now.
- [aide] We need to see the President.
He needs to be told.
- This is a matter of life and death.
- What is going on?
The Soviets' early detection system
picked up our new nukes.
[White House staffer] What new nukes?
[CJCS] A hundred warheads
just went online, ready to launch.
They're taking this as an act of war.
Prepping to return fire.
Return? What?
We haven't done anything.
That's not how it looks.
And we'd fire for less.
[man 1 ] Are you kidding me?
You blew through that light right there!
You didn't even see!
[man 2] How do you not see that?
[reporter]
Riots across the world erupting
as America and the Soviet Union
end communication,
declaring war!
No one knows any more than that.
But as you can imagine
with what's at stake,
there has been madness down here
in downtown Washington, D.C.
The national guard
has been brought in...
[National Guard officer on PA]
Attention! Attention!
By executive order, all civilians
must immediately evacuate
the Pennsylvania Avenue corridor
between 3rd and 12th streets northwest.
- [people clamoring]
- [indistinct radio chatter]
[preacher] It is the final days
of tribulation
that is happening to us now.
Can you see
what your sinfulness has done?
Your greed?
You gotta do something!
Come on! This way! Come on!
[woman] Riley!
[officer] All units.
Riley!
[officer] We need help.
- It's chaos out here.
- [woman] Riley!
What do you want me to do?
I don't know what to do.
Somebody help me.
[both panting]
Diana.
Diana, listen to me.
I had a great life.
Steve...
And you only made it better.
But you know what you need to do.
The world needs you.
- All right?
- No.
Yeah.
[Wonder Woman crying]
I'll never love again.
I pray that isn't true.
There's a wonderful,
big world out there.
- This crazy new world.
- [whimpers]
And I am so happy I got to see it...
but it deserves you.
I can't say goodbye.
You don't have to.
I'm already gone.
[Wonder Woman sobs]
I'll always love you, Diana,
no matter where I am.
I love you.
[breathing heavily]
I renounce my wish.
[crying]
[yelling]
[screams]
[gasping]
[Steve] It's easy.
It's only wind and air...
and how to ride it.
How to catch it.
You made a wish too, huh?
[Maxwell laughing]
They're a bitch, aren't they?
Make you pay a price,
but I've never been one for rules.
Luckily, I have a way to reverse it.
The answer is always more.
But you only get one wish.
But I, my dear, grant the wishes.
So I take what I want in return.
There's nothing in this world
someone doesn't have.
I'll rebuild my health, wish by wish,
organ by organ...
if I have to.
I'll be invincible.
Tell me,
what do you want?
I'm feeling generous.
I don't want to be like anyone anymore.
I want to be number one.
An apex predator,
like nothing there's ever been before.
I like the way you think.
Go on.
[indistinct chattering]
[Maxwell] You heard we were coming,
I presume?
How many broadcasting signals
can I take over at once?
Well, as many as you like, sir.
I'll take all of them.
All of them?
And I sure wish this works for me.
Don't you?
Yes, sir.
[wind whooshing]
Lights, camera...
Okay, stations 12,
9, 16, go transmit.
I need it now.
16, 9, 12. Do you receive?
[army technician]
Copy. Maximum power.
[head technician]
Okay. Moving forward now.
Global transmission in five,
four, three, two...
Citizens of the world,
allow me to introduce myself.
I am Max Lord,
and I'm here to change your life.
All you have to do...
is make a wish.
Anything you want.
Anything you dream of, you can have it.
If you can dream it...
Daddy?
...you can achieve it.
So just look into my eyes...
and make a wish.
Anything you dream of,
- have it.
- [speaking Mandarin]
[Maxwell in English] Right now.
- Do you want to be rich?
- [fans clamoring]
Do you want to be powerful?
[Irishman] Yeah, yeah. Whatever you say.
- [Maxwell] Say it out loud!
- You know what I wish?
- What? What?
- I wish all you Irish bastards
would get sent back
to where you came from!
Yeah? Well, I wish you'd drop dead!
- [woman groaning]
- [Maxwell] Look around you.
- Make your wish!
- [people making wishes]
Take what's yours.
Whatever you want,
you can have it.
- I wish for a million dollars.
- [men speak other languages]
[Maxwell in English] Wish for it.
[people continue making wishes]
[Maxwell] Anything you want.
Anything you dream of, have it.
[laughing] Yes.
I can hear it.
[continues laughing] I hear you.
Yes, say it.
Say it out loud.
[echoing] That's right. "I wish."
Take it.
Take it. It's all yours.
It's all yours for the taking!
[people continue making wishes]
[labored breathing]
And I... I take your health
and your strength.
Give her your rage
and your prowess.
And I take your power.
I take your life force.
Yes.
Yes!
[echoing] That's right.
You're doing great.
[Maxwell laughing]
It's all yours.
I wish you were here, Daddy.
I wish you'd come back. Daddy, please!
- All you have to do is wish for it.
- I'm still here, Daddy.
Daddy, please!
[Wonder Woman] Barbara.
What did you do?
[growls]
[Cheetah roars]
[Cheetah grunts]
[both grunting]
[snarling]
[Cheetah] No.
You renounced your wish.
I had to. And so do you.
Nothing good is born from lies, Barbara.
We're wasting precious time.
Even now, patronizing me.
[growls]
[both grunting]
[Wonder Woman yelps]
[gasping]
[Cheetah growls]
- [yells]
- [Wonder Woman] Barbara...
I know you're in there.
Please. Please, renounce your wish.
It's over.
- [both grunting]
- Please!
Renounce your wish.
Never!
Then I'm so sorry.
[muffled screaming]
[Cheetah groaning]
[people making wishes]
[Maxwell] That's right.
- Just wish for it.
- [wind whooshing]
It's yours now.
All you have to do is say it out loud.
Make a wish. Any wish.
Look into my eyes,
and everything you've been waiting for,
it's all yours.
You're too late.
[people continue making wishes]
- [Wonder Woman grunting]
- Granted.
Granted.
Granted!
- Granted.
- Why are you doing this?
Don't you have enough?
Why not more?
Why not wish for more?
But they don't know
what you're taking from them.
We want what we want.
Just like you did.
So make a wish.
Very good.
[laughing]
[people continue making wishes]
[grunting]
Granted.
It's too late, Diana.
They already heard me.
Already wished!
And those that haven't yet...
[laughing]
Oh, they will!
[moaning]
[grunting]
- [Maxwell laughing]
- [grunts]
Granted.
[groaning]
[people continue making wishes]
Poor Diana.
Why be such a hero?
You could have kept your pilot
and your powers,
if only you'd join me.
Wanna reconsider? [laughing]
I'm a forgiving man!
You want him back?
Just say the word.
You can have it all!
You just have to want it!
I've never wanted anything more.
But he's gone...
and that's the truth.
And everything has a price.
One I'm not willing to pay.
Not anymore.
This world was a beautiful place
just as it was...
and you cannot have it all.
You can only have the truth.
And the truth is enough.
The truth is beautiful.
So look at this world...
and look at what your wish
is costing it.
You must be the hero.
Only you can save the day.
Renounce your wish
if you want to save this world.
Why would I...
when it's finally my turn?
The world belongs to me!
You can't stop me. No one can!
I wasn't talking to you.
[grunts]
I was talking to everyone else.
Because you're not the only one
who has suffered.
Who wants more.
Who wants them back.
Who doesn't want to be afraid anymore.
Or alone.
[Maxwell] Stop!
Cut the signal! Stop!
Or frightened.
Or powerless.
'Cause you're not the only one
who imagined a world
where everything was different.
[Maxwell's father shouting in Spanish]
[Maxwell's mother groans]
[Wonder Woman in English] Better.
- Finally.
- [shouting continues]
A world where they were loved
and seen, and appreciated.
Finally.
[boy 1 ] Oh, my God. Who is he?
He doesn't even speak English.
What is he eating?
Look at his shoes!
[boys laughing]
[boy 2] Weirdo!
[Wonder Woman]
But what is it costing you?
Do you see the truth?
[men shouting]
[siren wailing]
[Alistair] Daddy!
- Daddy!
- [man shouting in Russian]
[in English] The Russians are launching.
We've got orders to counter.
All right, all right.
- [siren blaring]
- [people gasping]
Alistair!
[car horn blaring]
[announcer on PA] Emergency alert.
You have four minutes to find shelter.
[man shouting]
Alistair!
My son!
[announcer] Stay calm and stay indoors.
Alistair!
[Alistair] Daddy! Daddy!
Help me, Daddy!
[announcer] This is not a test.
Daddy!
[alarm blaring]
[announcer] One-minute warning.
Wait. My son!
I can see my son!
Save him, Max.
I have to save my son.
[Alistair] Daddy!
Alistair.
Daddy!
My... Alistair.
I renounce my wish!
I renounce my wish.
We have missiles disappearing, sir.
Yes, sir.
They are vanishing from our screen.
[news anchor]
Only just hearing now that a ceasefire
between the Soviet Union
and the United States
has averted a global nuclear crisis.
[news anchors speaking other languages]
[in English] I renounce my wish.
- I take back my wish.
- I renounce my wish.
[people renouncing in other languages]
[breathing heavily]
[in English] Alistair!
Alistair!
[Alistair] Daddy!
- Daddy!
- Alistair!
Alistair.
Oh, Alistair, Alistair.
I'm so sorry, baby.
I'm so glad I wished you'd come.
I knew it would work.
No.
That is not why I'm back.
I've been lying to you.
I'm not a great guy.
In fact, I'm a pretty messed up,
loser guy.
And I made terrible mistakes.
But you...
you don't ever have to make a wish
for me to love you.
I'm here because I love you.
I just...
I just wish and I pray that, one day,
I'll be able to make you proud enough
that you'll be able to forgive me.
And love me.
Because I'm nothing
to be proud of, Alistair.
I don't need you to make me proud.
I already love you, Daddy.
You're my dad.
[Maxwell sobs]
- Sorry. Sorry.
- Sorry.
It's okay. [laughs] It's okay.
[children laughing]
[man gasping in awe]
So beautiful.
[chuckles] Sorry.
Just talking to myself.
It's all right.
It's just that...
It's wonderful. It's so many things.
Yeah.
I know what you mean.
I like your...
I like your outfit.
You like...
Thanks.
You know, my friends...
they kinda tease me about it,
but it works, right?
- You look great.
- Thank you.
You just made my day.
- Happy holidays. See you around.
- Happy holidays.
[sighs]
[imperceptible]
So many things.
So, so many things.
[siren wailing]
[indistinct chattering]
- [man 1 ] Whoa!
- [man 2] Look out!
[people screaming]
Oh, my God.
- Mom, would you take her?
- Yeah.
Um, excuse me.
Excuse me. Please, you have to let me
thank you, Miss...
Asteria.
Asteria. Wow. That's a beautiful name.
It's from my culture.
I can't thank you enough.
I mean, you saved my daughter.
How did you do that?
It's just a simple shift of weight.
Takes practice.
But I've been doing this a long time.
[gasps]